(Raj:)Then my dad said
based on their
(Raj:)love life, she should know
about phoning it in.
(Bernadette:)He said that to her?
Well, they weren't
speaking at the time,
(Raj:)so he had a servant
say it to her.
(Raj:)Oh, maybe I could
make a gift for them.
(Raj:)I know how much you guys love
the coasters I made for you.
(Bernadette:)They're yours in the divorce.
(Leonard:)Hey. What're you working on?
(Sheldon:)Remember when I said
if you went through
(Sheldon:)with your surgery, there was a
one-in-700,000 chance of dying?
(Leonard:)Yeah...?
(Sheldon:)Well, I've been
crunching the numbers,
(Sheldon:)and so far, I've gotten
your probability of death
(Sheldon:)all the way to a
sphincter-tightening
(Sheldon:)one in 300.
(Leonard:)Great timing.
My "check sphincter"
light just went on.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, what if you have
an allergic reaction
(Sheldon:)to the surgeon's latex gloves?
I'm not
(Leonard:)allergic to latex.
(Sheldon:)Well, then why don't you
wear the rubber gloves
(Sheldon:)I bought for you
to do the dishes?